<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>true on Drone DPG Toolkit</title>
    <link>https://unicef.github.io/drone-4sdgtoolkit/downloadbtn/true/</link>
    <description>Recent content in true on Drone DPG Toolkit</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Creative Commons BY-SA 4.0. Site theme maintained by UNICEF. Original theme, Dot, created by ThemeFisher.</copyright><atom:link href="https://unicef.github.io/drone-4sdgtoolkit/downloadbtn/true/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Analytics</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/drone-4sdgtoolkit/analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/drone-4sdgtoolkit/analytics/</guid>
      <description>“Be Data Driven”.
One of the main products that from drones is data; data is key for impact assessment or decision-making. The “Analytics” section of this toolkit centres on curating drone-related artificial intelligence and data products that inform decision-making. Areas where these drone analytics tools are used include surveillance, research, operations, project management and impact evaluation.
Analytics Tools &amp;ndash; Coming soon
Submit open datasets to the UNICEF drones for SDGs toolkit</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guides</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/drone-4sdgtoolkit/guides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/drone-4sdgtoolkit/guides/</guid>
      <description>“Reuse and Improve”.
The global drone industry has been developing for decades and the lessons learned from various stakeholders can be a guide for future innovation. UNICEF and several other stakeholders have made significant contributions to the global knowledge base of the technology and use of drones in the development and humanitarian contexts specifically. The “Guides” section is a collection of case studies, annual reports, and action guides for achieving specific outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/drone-4sdgtoolkit/learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/drone-4sdgtoolkit/learning/</guid>
      <description>“Design with the user”.
The future of drone use will always be in the hands of the next generation. The “Learning” section is a collection of drone technology learning resources. The courseware is from UNICEF drone education initiatives or open source courseware from other partners.
Learning Tools Africa Drone and Data Academy
The African Drone and Data Academy (ADDA) aims to be a center of excellence that will equip African youth with necessary 21st-century skills while strengthening the drone ecosystem for more effective humanitarian and development response.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regulations</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/drone-4sdgtoolkit/regs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/drone-4sdgtoolkit/regs/</guid>
      <description>“Build for sustainability” and “Do no harm”.
Drones operate in public airspace, which is a very sensitive environment. This presents unique challenges and risks. National Civil Aviation Authorities handle the management of public airspace with support from the International Civil Aviation Organization. The “Regulations” section of the toolkit houses several international best practice documents for the safe management, monitoring and control of drone operations in public airspace.
Regulation tools ICAO Model UAS Regulations</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/drone-4sdgtoolkit/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/drone-4sdgtoolkit/software/</guid>
      <description>“Use Open Source” and “Design for scale”.
Using only Open Source is a key principle of UNICEF Innovation, and all of our investments in software and other products have reflected this. The “Software” section is a curation of various drone software products from UNICEF Innovation cohort companies.
Software Portable UTM
Portable UTM is an Open Source-based Unmanned Traffic Management System developed following NASA UAS Service Supplier Specification.
  Humanitarian Purposes Drones have proven their importance in medicine delivery, disaster recovery, and public safety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startups</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/drone-4sdgtoolkit/startups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/drone-4sdgtoolkit/startups/</guid>
      <description>“Understand the existing ecosystem” and “Be Collaborative”.
The “Startups” section contains company information and stories about UNICEF Drone Startups. This section aims to highlight our drone investees and their work with UNICEF Country Offices or other development partners.
UNICEF Venture Fund Startups Coming soon…
Principles of the Drones for SDGs Toolkit </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
